<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<BBKR_string xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
<![CDATA[LGE AppStore End-User Terms and Conditions 
LG Electronics Australia Pty Limited ACN 064 531 264, (“LGE” or “we”) welcomes you to the LGE AppStore (the “LGE AppStore”), which it provides to you, the end-user (either “you” or “End-User”), to access, browse, download, use and/or pay for Applications to enhance your experience with any internet enabled consumer electronics product that is manufactured by LGE and/or its Affiliates (“LGE Internet Enabled Product”). Please read these LGE AppStore End-User Terms and Conditions (the “Agreement”) and the Application License Agreement. TO AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THE AGREEMENT AND THE APPLICATION LICENSE AGREEMENT, CLICK “AGREE.”  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, DO NOT CLICK “AGREE,” AND DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE LGE APPSTORE
LGE may change the terms of the Agreement from time to time. By continuing to access, browse, download, use and/or pay for Applications in the LGE AppStore after we post any such changes, you accept the Agreement as modified. We may change, restrict access to, suspend or discontinue the LGE AppStore, or any of the Applications, at any time. 
LGE respects the privacy of its End-Users. Please take a few minutes to review our Privacy Policy for the LGE AppStore [http://au.lgappstv.com/appspc/footer/footer/movePrivacyView.lge]. 
You must be at least 14 (fourteen) years of age to use or access the LGE AppStore. If you are at least 14 but under the age of 18, you must have your parent or legal guardian’s permission to use or access the LGE AppStore. 
The following terms and conditions apply to your use of the LGE AppStore, your purchase of products (each, an “Application”) through the LGE AppStore, and your use of such Applications. Before using, downloading from or otherwise accessing the LGE AppStore or any Application, either through your LGE Internet Enabled Product or PC, carefully read this Agreement. The Applications provided through the LGE AppStore are licensed by the application provider of the Application (“Application Provider”) to you, the original End-User, solely for your personal use as set forth below and subject to any applicable End-User application license agreement (“EULA”).  If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, do not use, download from or otherwise access the LGE AppStore. 
1. Your LGE AppStore Account Membership
The LGE AppStore authorises two kinds of members to have access to the LGE AppStore content: Associate Members and Regular Members. 
a. Associate Members: Associate Members are those users who register and create an account through their LGE Internet Enabled Product (“Associate Member Account” or “Account”). Each Associate Member will create an account ID and password that may be used to access the LGE AppStore and download and use free apps. However, Associate Members will not be able to download Paid Applications (as defined below).  To create an Associate Member Account, you may be required to provide certain information about yourself (such as identification or contact details) as part of the registration process. Do not reveal your Associate Member Account information to anyone else. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of your Associate Member Account and for all activities that occur on or through your Associate Member Account. 
As an Associate Member, you agree: that you are solely responsible for (and LGE has no responsibility to you or any third party for) any breach of your Associate Member Account; to provide accurate and complete information when you create an Associate Member Account; to keep the information you provide accurate and complete; and to notify LGE immediately of any breach of your Associate Member Account.
Associate Members may not change any of the user information, or purchase Paid Applications.. An Associate Member may only make changes or modifications to his or her registration information or purchase Paid Applications, if the Associate Member converts the Associate Member Account into a Regular Member Account (as defined below) by accessing the LGE SmartTV service on your PC, submitting your Associate Member Account identification number and password and following the instructions. 
b. Regular Members: Regular Members are those users who create an account through their PC or convert their Associate Member Account (“Regular Member Account” or “Account” or collectively with Associate Member Account, “Accounts”). The holders of a Regular Member Account may: download free apps; purchase Paid Applications for download and use on any LGE Internet Enabled Product, including the LGE SmartTV, oBluRay player, etc; make changes to Account information; and cancel an Account.
To create a Regular Member Account, you may be required to provide information about yourself (such as identification or contact details) and credit card/payment information as part of the registration process. Do not reveal your Regular Member Account information to anyone else. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of your Regular Member Account and for all activities that occur on or through your Regular Member Account. You agree that you are solely responsible for (and LGE has no responsibility to you or any third party for) any breach of your Regular Member Account. 
Regular Members further agree: to provide accurate and complete information when you create a Regular Member Account; to keep the information you provide accurate and complete; and notify LGE immediately of any breach of your Regular Member Account.
2. Fees and Payment; Refunds; Coupons and Bonus Cash 
a. Fees and Payment, Generally: Applications are either available for download at no charge or, where available, require you pay a specific amount (“Paid Applications”). For Paid Applications, the LGE AppStore accepts payment mechanisms as listed on the payment page of the LGE AppStore (“Payment Mechanisms”). Only Regular Member Account holders may purchase and download Paid Applications. You agree to pay for all Paid Applications you purchase. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR THE TIMELY PAYMENT OF ALL FEES AND ANY APPLICABLE TAXES AND FOR PROVIDING LGE WITH A VALID PAYMENT MECHANISM FOR PAYMENT OF ALL FEES AND ANY APPLICABLE TAXES.  
b. Payment by Credit Card or Debit Card: To use a credit card or debit card (collectively, “Cards”) for purchase of Paid Applications, you will be required to provide accurate, current and complete Card  information before you will be permitted to download Paid Applications. You authorize LGE or its agents to charge or debit your Card with the specified amount plus Goods and Services Tax (“GST”), for each Paid Application you download. Once you enter a Card, such Card will be used for future transactions unless you designate a different Card. Debit cards and check cards have daily spending limits that may prevent the processing of your order. If the transaction is not accepted online, you will be unable to use that Card for your transaction and should use another Card. 
c. Refunds: Application prices and availability are subject to change at any time, and LGE will not provide price protection or refunds in the event of price reductions or promotional offerings. All sales of successfully downloaded Applications are final and non-refundable. In the event that a Paid Application is not available after the payment is confirmed by LGE but before the download, your sole remedy is a refund. If technical problems prevent or unreasonably delay delivery of your Paid Application, your exclusive and sole remedy is either a replacement of the Paid Application or a refund of the price you paid for the Paid Application, in LGE’s sole discretion. 
d. Bonus Cash and Coupons: From time to time, LGE or another third party may offer promotions that enable payment on the LGE AppStore through other payment mechanisms, e.g. Bonus Cash or Coupons. The terms of such offer will be given at the time the offer is made. 
3. Your Use of LGE AppStore and Apps; Access 
You agree to use the LGE AppStore and the Applications only for personal, noncommercial use. You agree not to access or attempt to access the LGE AppStore by means other than through the interface or software that is provided by LGE, unless LGE specifically authorizes you do to so by written agreement. You agree not to modify the interface or software in any manner, or use modified versions of the software, for any purposes including obtaining unauthorized access to the LGE AppStore. You may not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the LGE AppStore or any Applications downloaded from the LGE AppStore, except and only to the extent that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law. 
YOU SHALL BE AUTHORIZED TO DOWNLOAD AND USE EACH APPLICATION ON NO MORE THAN FIVE (5) DEVICES PER ACCOUNT WITHIN 12 MONTH FROM INITIAL PURCHASE DATE SUBJECT TO  VALIDITY OF ORIGINAL LICENSE. FOR THE AVOIDANCE OF DOUBT, AN ASSOCIATE MEMBER ACCOUNT CONVERTED TO A REGULAR MEMBER ACCOUNT IS TO BE TREATED AS ONE (1) ACCOUNT. Except as otherwise provided below, you may not modify or alter the Application in any way, and may only use the Application as expressly set forth above and as set forth in the applicable EULA for the Application, if any. You agree that you will not engage in activities that interfere with or disrupt the LGE AppStore, any services offered through an Application, or any other server, network, service or website associated with any LGE Internet Enabled Product or the LGE AppStore. 
Access to and downloading from the LGE AppStore requires at least an LGE Internet Enabled Product and an Internet connection. You will not be able to access and download Paid Applications from the LGE AppStore unless you are a Regular Member, as defined in this Agreement. In addition, your use of certain Applications may require an Internet connection. LGE is not responsible for costs associated with your use of an Internet connection.
4. LGE’s Rights 
LGE reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to add, remove, disable access to, block, or modify the LGE AppStore, and to add, remove, disable access to, block, or modify remotely any Applications previously downloaded to your device from the LGE AppStore, including for reasons of changes to obligations or restrictions with third parties, an Application Provider’s violation of an Agreement with LGE, or due to a court order. LGE may limit the use of or access to certain features or portions of the LGE AppStore or Applications downloaded from the LGE AppStore, in its sole discretion and without notice or liability. If LGE removes, disables access to, or otherwise blocks you from accessing an Application, you will need to contact the Application Provider for further action. 
LGE has the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any materials submitted by you or otherwise available on the LGE AppStore or in the Applications, to investigate any reported or apparent violation of this Agreement, and to take action that LGE in its sole discretion deems appropriate, including, without limitation, suspension or termination of Accounts hereunder. If your Account is suspended, you may not cancel your Account until such time as your Account is eligible for reinstatement, in LGE’s sole discretion. 
5. Intellectual Property Rights
You agree that the LGE AppStore and the Applications available through the LGE AppStore, including but not limited to the graphics, editorial content, audio clips, video clips, and software, contain proprietary information and material that is owned by LGE, Application Providers, or other third parties. Neither you nor anyone acting on your behalf, acquire any intellectual property rights or other proprietary rights, including patents, designs, trademarks, copyrights or trade secrets relating to the contents in the LGE AppStore or in the Applications, except as expressly specified in an appropriate license or mutually agreed upon in writing. 
6. Third Party Materials and Objectionable Content
You understand, acknowledge and agree that certain Applications may provide access to products, services, web content or other third-party materials and that LGE is not responsible for such third party content.  You agree that LGE is not responsible for examining or evaluating the third party content or the accuracy of such content. LGE does not make any representations or warranties regarding, and accepts no liability in respect of, such third party content. 
You understand, acknowledge, and agree that by accessing and using the LGE AppStore and Applications that you may encounter material that you may deem explicit or offensive, indecent or objectionable to you, and that you may not be warned about such material in advance.  You agree that your downloading and use of all Applications will be at your sole risk, and LGE shall have no liability to you as a result of any exposure through such Applications. 
7. Reviews 
LGE may permit users to post reviews of Applications on the LGE AppStore. These reviews express opinions of the reviewer only and do not reflect the opinions of LGE.  LGE makes no representations or warranties as to the accuracy or completeness of the reviews. You agree that LGE shall have no liability to you if you rely on the reviews to download or use an Application. LGE reserves the right to, but has no obligation to remove reviews that LGE deems irrelevant or otherwise inappropriate for any reason. 
If you post a review, you hereby grant LGE a perpetual, worldwide, fully transferable and sub-licensable, irrevocable, royalty-free license to make, use, sell, market, reproduce, create derivative works of, distribute, perform, and display the review in any manner and for any purpose. You acknowledge that your personally identifiable information may be associated with your review unless you post the review anonymously. If you post a review, you agree not to post, publish or transmit any material that: (i) is false or misleading; (ii) is defamatory; (iii) invades another’s privacy; (iv) is obscene, pornographic, or offensive; (v) promotes bigotry, racism, hatred or harm against any individual or group; (vi) infringes on another’s rights, including but not limited to any intellectual property rights; or (vii) violates, or encourages any conduct that would violate any applicable law or regulation or would give rise to civil liability. 
8. Indemnification
To the maximum extent permitted by law, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold LGE, its directors, officers, employees, affiliates, and agents harmless from and against any and all claims arising out of your breach of this Agreement, your use of the LGE AppStore, or your use of any Applications downloaded from the LGE AppStore. 
9.  Warranty and Disclaimers 
To the full extent permitted by law LGE excludes all representations, warranties, terms and conditions, whether express or implied (and including, without limitation, those implied by statute, custom, law or otherwise), except as expressly set out in this Agreement.    LGE acknowledges that the Applications come with guarantees that cannot be excluded under the Australian Consumer Law.  You are entitled to a replacement or refund for a major failure of an Application or compensation for any other reasonably forseeable loss or damage arising out of the failure of the Application.  You are also entitled to have the Application replaced if it fails to be of acceptable quality and the failure does not amount to a major failure.
10. Term and Termination
This Agreement is effective until terminated. LGE may terminate this Agreement in whole or as it applies to your use of any Application or the LGE AppStore if you breach any of the terms of this Agreement. You may terminate it at any time by cancelling your Account, provided that your Account is not in suspension and provided that any terms relating to your use of each Application will survive unless and until you destroy all copies of such Application and related documentation. In addition, LGE reserves the right to modify, suspend, or discontinue the LGE AppStore (or any part or content thereof) at any time with or without notice to you, for any reason whatsoever, and LGE will not be liable to you or to any third party should it exercise such rights. 
If you cancel your Account, you may register for another Account at any time, but you cannot use your prior Account ID for a period of three (3) months from the date of cancellation. If a former Account holder registers again, even under the same Account ID, his or her prior information is not able to be recovered, including any cash or credits available at the time of cancellation. 
11. Miscellaneous Provisions 
a. Governing law: This Agreement is governed by the laws of New South Wales, Australia and each party irrevocably and unconditionally submits to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of that State.
b. Severability: In the event any provision of this Agreement is found to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable, the validity, legality and enforceability of any of the remaining provisions shall not in any way be affected or impaired. 
c. Enforcement of Agreement: LGE reserves the right to takes any steps it believes to be reasonably necessary or appropriate to enforce and/or verify compliance with any part of this Agreement. You agree that LGE has the right, without liability to you, to disclose any information relating to your use of the LGE AppStore to law enforcement authorities, government officials, and/or a third party, as LGE believes is reasonably necessary or appropriate to enforce and/or verify compliance with any part of this Agreement. 
d. Dispute Resolution: Any dispute, controversy or claim arising out of, relating to or in connection with this Agreement including any question regarding its existence, validity or termination shall be resolved by arbitration in accordance with the ACICA Arbitration Rules.  The seat of arbitration shall be Sydney, Australia.  The number of arbitrators shall be 1.
e. Entire Agreement: By accepting this Agreement, you agree that the Agreement (including all incorporated or referenced documents) set forth the entire agreement between you and LGE, and supersede all prior agreements, whether written or oral, with respect to the LGE AppStore and all Applications, notwithstanding the terms or conditions of any such prior agreements. If LGE fails to enforce any right or provision in this Agreement, such failure will not constitute a waiver of such right or provision
Should you have any issues or questions regarding the LGE AppStore, please visit [http://au.lgappstv.com/appspc/support/support/retrieveNoticeList.lge]. Please note that LGE does not provide support for the Applications and you should contact the Application Provider directly. 
LAST UPDATED: [2010/12/10]
APPLICATION LICENSE AGREEMENT
THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS APPLY TO YOUR USE OF EACH APPLICATION YOU DOWNLOAD FROM THE LGE APPSTORE (EACH, AN “APPLICATION”) AND SUPPLEMENT THE LGE APPSTORE END-USER TERMS AND CONDITIONS. BEFORE USING ANY APPLICATION, CAREFULLY READ THIS AGREEMENT. 
You acknowledge that the license granted hereunder is granted to you by the provider of the Application (“Application Provider”) and not by LG Electronics Australia Pty Limited (“LGE”). If the Application Provider provides an End User License Agreement (“EULA”) with the Application, those terms shall supplement this Application License Agreement. As between you and the Application Provider, any additional or different terms in such EULA shall take precedence over the terms in this Application License Agreement. 
You acknowledge and agree that LGE is a third party beneficiary of this Application License Agreement and any EULA, if so provided. You acknowledge and agree that LGE will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the right) to enforce such license against you as a third party beneficiary of those agreements. 
1. Grant of License: You are hereby granted a limited, non-transferable license to use the Application on any LGE Internet Enabled Product and in the manner set forth in the LGE AppStore End-User Terms and Conditions. You may not rent, lease, lend, sell, redistribute or sublicense the Application. You may not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the Application, except and only to the extent that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law. Any attempt to do so is a violation of the rights of the Application Provider. If you breach this restriction, you may be subject to prosecution and damages. The terms of the license will govern any upgrades provided by the Application Provider that replace and/or supplement the original Application, unless such upgrade is accompanied by a separate license in which case the terms of that license will govern. The Application Provider reserves all rights in and to the Application not expressly granted to you under this Application License Agreement. 
2. Consent to Use of Data: You agree that the Application Provider may collect and use technical and related information, gathered in any manner, as part of product support services related to the Application. The Application Provider may use this information solely to improve its products or to provide customized services or technologies to you. The Application Provider may disclose this information to others, but not in a form that personally identifies you. 
3. Termination: The license is effective until terminated by you or the Application Provider. Your rights under this license will terminate automatically without notice from the Application Provider if you fail to comply with any term(s) of this license. Upon termination of the license, you must cease all use of the Application, and destroy all copies, full or partial, of the Application, including any accompanying documentation. 
4. Third Party Material; Objectionable Content: You understand, acknowledge and agree that certain Applications may provide access to products, services, web content or other third-party materials and that LGE is not responsible for such third party content.  You agree that LGE is not responsible for examining or evaluating the third party content or the accuracy of such content. LGE does not make any representations or warranties regarding, and accepts no liability in respect of, such third party content. 
You understand, acknowledge, and agree that by accessing and downloading Applications from the LGE AppStore that you may encounter material that you may deem explicit or offensive, indecent or objectionable to you, and that you may not be warned about such material in advance.  You agree that your downloading and use of all Applications will be at your sole risk, and LGE shall have no liability to you as a result of any exposure through such Applications. 
5. WARRANTIES AND DISCLAIMERS: To the full extent permitted by law LGE excludes all representations, warranties, terms and conditions, whether express or implied (and including, without limitation, those implied by statute, custom, law or otherwise), except as expressly set out in this Agreement.    LGE acknowledges that the Applications come with guarantees that cannot be excluded under the Australian Consumer Law.  You are entitled to a replacement or refund for a major failure of an Application or compensation for any other reasonably foreseeable loss or damage arising out of the failure of the Application.  You are also entitled to have the Application replaced if it fails to be of acceptable quality and the failure does not amount to a major failure. 
7.  This Application License Agreement is governed by the laws of New South Wales, Australia and each party irrevocably and unconditionally submits to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of that State.
8.  By accepting this Application License Agreement, you agree that such agreement (including all incorporated or referenced documents) sets forth the entire agreement between you and the Application Provider, and supersedes all prior agreements, whether written or oral, with respect to the Application, notwithstanding the terms or conditions of any such prior agreements. If the Application Provider fails to enforce any right or provision in this Application License Agreement, such failure will not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. 
LAST UPDATED: [2010/12/10] 
]]>
</BBKR_string>